<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!--can be updated with CDATA-->

    <string name="practice_category_autoreport">Autogenic trainings</string>
    <string name="practice_category_meditations">Meditations</string>
    <string name="practice_category_spiritual">Spiritual practices</string>

    <string name="practice_category_autoreport_description">Autotrenig in itself is precisely self-awareness, a shift of
        yours “I” from the secondary consciousness to the primary and work with the primary consciousness at the level
        of primary consciousness. Now we call him in a certain transformed, altered form - an autogenous training,
        thanks to Schultz, as we already said. But it works at the level of primary consciousness, therefore various
        changes occur in the body and etc.
    </string>

    <string name="practice_category_meditations_description">Meditation is a more complicated practice. We work with the
        help of the primary consciousness with the secondary, we study the system, practically being in the system,
        delving deeper, only leaving it slightly, we begin to study it, but without harm to ourselves. And meditation in
        itself, whatever it is, it just remains meditation. This is work at the level of primary consciousness.
    </string>

    <string name="practice_category_spiritual_description">Spiritual practice - "it is when the Personality going beyond
        the limits on which consciousness can function." This is precisely what develops the Person. This is observing
        the primary consciousness, the secondary consciousness, all their combinations, manifestations, self-awareness
        of oneself as part of the Spiritual World. This is the perception of the Spiritual World. Well, and as the
        ultimate goal - it is a merger with the Spiritual World or becoming part of It.
    </string>

    <string name="shultz_autoreport_title">Schultz Autogenic training</string>
    <string name="shultz_autoreport">shultz_autoreport_en</string>

    <string name="altered_consciousness_state_title">Altered state of consciousness</string>
    <string name="altered_consciousness_state">altered_consciousness_state_en</string>

    <string name="concetration_of_attention_title">Meditation for concentration of attention</string>
    <string name="concetration_of_attention">concetration_of_attention_en</string>

    <string name="know_yourself_title">Know yourself</string>
    <string name="know_yourself">Not ready yet</string>

    <string name="kuvshin_title">Jug</string>
    <string name="kuvshin">kuvshin_en</string>

    <string name="lotus_love_bl_title">«Lotus Flower»: Love and Gratitude</string>
    <string name="lotus_love_bl">lotus_love_bl_en</string>

    <string name="lotus_title">Lotus Flower</string>
    <string name="lotus">lotus_en</string>

    <string name="chetverik_title">Chetverik</string>
    <string name="chetverik">chetverik_en</string>

    <string name="pyramid_title">Pyramid</string>
    <string name="pyramid">pyramid_en</string>

</resources>